Yep, the successfully completed the configuration of our Linux and VisualBox.
So now, we are going to use calling Linux as a attacking machine in our scenario that
was a hacker machine and we are a hackers, and we are going to use a Windows machine.
So, Windows machine is a target machine so we are going to practice our routine exercise
and offensive or defensive exercise in the Windows machine.
So, you don't need to download any kind of external thing.
I already configured, I already uploaded that in my cloud platform and I will be giving this
link and you can also utilize that and you can download it, okay.
I have attached this link in, yep, I am going to attach this link in my Udemy video, let
me into that quickly.
So you can check this, okay, you have all the links that are present in this, okay.
So, this video, I have occurred after completing all the other sections, let's go for
a Windows machine.
So, once you, this Windows machine is like nearly 40 gigabytes GB, so I already downloaded
it.
So, once you download the Windows machine, so nothing units to do, you just need to double
click on this, okay.
Let's do that, finish it off, it was started importing, it will take some time to complete
the import, okay.
I will post, I will post this video and I will do some on the import has been succeeded.
Now the machine was imported and let's start the VM, let's change the network settings
to this one, yeah.
So, the password is password, okay, PASW already, no capital, everything small, EASW already,
password is password, this is the console you will get, everything, every software,
every applications, everything which I have used that will be present here, okay, every
application, every exploitation, related software, programs, scripts, everything you
can find in this machine, okay, so yeah, that's what you don't need to check, you don't
need to search outside, anything, everything will be in the machine, so let's hop up from
here because we configured everything, let's jump on to the next video, bye bye.